Mauricio Carpio LinkedIn GitHub Upwork

Devops Enginner with more than **6 years** experience both in site reliability positions, Cloud Enginneer and development in the cloud. Working with **Python**, **Golang** and **C** as programming languages. My experience varys in working with many cloud services as **AWS**, **AZURE**.

My objective is work on a project as Devops or Cloud Enginneer learning and developing better solutions for deployment and quality of Working as a UPWORK freelancer i had any projects and works done with many clients satisfied, and more than 20k in profits here is my profile link.

Peru, Lima
La Molina 1575
+1 704 753 7650
icarpioherrera@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Edwards Lifesciences - Cloud Enginneer - California

November 2022 - Present

- Automatize workflow in CI/CD pipeline for deploying services, increasing saving time for deployment up to 50%.
- Introduce AI analysis into our pipeline for deployment in AWS services with Terraform for code analysis and bugs.
- Working with troubleshooting bugs and problems in production environment with more than 1000 nodes.
- Scripting and developing solution for engineers to agilize their work in the cloud and RedHat..

Radical alpha -Devops Engineer/Cloud Enginneer - Paris/France

March 2022 - November 2022

- Reduce cost of AWS bill up to 50%, managing the account and improving the infrastructure with Terraform. Improving the code and execution of RDS databases a and moving some of the data to S3.
- Improving the velocity and algorithms for trading up to 3x times in python and golang.
- Moving 100% of the infrastructure that was created in console to IaC.

OttoAI - Devops Engineer - New York - Startup Project

Jan 2022 - March 2022

- Design microservices infrastructure for escalability with Front-end and Backend in ECS, Apigateway, loadbalancer, route53 and lambda
- Deployment of many services in production environment with IaC and troubleshoting problems in both envi
- Developing in Python APIs for consumption in apigateway with Cognito auth, deploymen of them in terraform in production and developer environment.

Qortor Cloud Engineer - Los Angeles - **Startup Project**

April 2021 - Jan 2022

- Complete design and deploy of a microservices infrastructure with CI/CD build with ECS, APIGATEWAY, LOADBALANCER, COGNITO, LAMBDA, SQS, SNS, APP MESH and KUBERNETES.
- Work with a teams of front-end developers and backend syncronizing realises of services in agile. Helping with debugging and development of those services
- Building, maintaining and improving the cloud with IaC. Organizing accounts with aws organizations.

CERTIFICATIONS



TECHNOLOGIES

AWS and AZURE for fast development and use of services -- 4 years

Terraform, Cloudformation Ansible as IaC. -- 4 years

Gitlab, **github**, **bitbucket** for CI/CD pipelines - 4 years

Golang and Python for rapid development of APIs in the cloud -- 5 years

Kubernetes, ECS and docker for deploying microservices. -4 Years

Redhat , Linux , Unix administration. 4 Years

Languajes

Staircase — Cloud Engineer / Senior lambda developer - San Francisco

February 2021 - April 2021

• Working as a developer in PYTHON deploying lambdas applications in the cloud.

- Developing APIs in the services that interact with ASANA and GITHUB for different services.
- Bringing solutions for problems in the cloud with differents services related to aws.

Bwit Solutions - Bank Interbank — Devops Engineer - Startup Project

December 2019 - February 2021

- Design infrastructure in the cloud with serverless design, lambda, sqs and s3.
- Working with security measures for sensitive data, in amazon glue, firehose and RDS
- Deploy infrastructure and applications in production environment with terraform.

MiBolsillo, Remote— Golang Developer - Lima

October 2018 - December 2019

- Development APIs in Golang and deployment of them in the Cloud
- Working with GRPCs for microservices and docker for deployment.

PROJECTS

Fastblog, Remote— Python AI Developer / Tech Lead <u>www.fastblog.ai</u> - Austria

January 2023 - now

- Development APIs in python and deployment of them in AWS
- Working with GPT4, GPT3 api with langehain for LLM models.
- Using langachain, fastapi, django for deployment of apis into AWS, build documentation, working with developers and organize realizes
- Working with developing and recolecting data for the creation of new AI models.

EDUCATION

ISIL, Peru, Lima— Software Engineer

January 2016 - March 2018

Software Engineer and the basics of computer science with hands on experience in web development.

42 Silicon Valley , California , Bay Area — Software Engineer

February 2018 - February 2019

As the program called "Piscine" is mentioned, the strongest are kept afloat, submerged in four intensive weeks of coding from Monday to Sunday, day and night, developing problems in Unix and C language.

C, Golang, Terraform, Python, Bash, Java, SQL,